{
    "subject": "Witold_Leszczy\u0144ski",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "Matthew's_Days",
    "human_readable": "Witold Leszczy\u0144ski directed the film Matthew's Days.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9790255427360535,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Witold Leszczy\u0144ski."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9526612162590027,
            "question": "What is the title of the film directed by Witold Leszczy\u0144ski?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9507272839546204,
            "question": "Is Witold Leszczy\u0144ski a film director?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8962725400924683,
            "question": "Who directed the film Matthew's Days?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5756106972694397,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the plot of Matthew's Days?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5479903221130371,
            "question": "When was Matthew's Days released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5375519394874573,
            "question": "Where was Matthew's Days filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5291695594787598,
            "question": "What kind of work did Witold Leszczy\u0144ski create?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4667675495147705,
            "question": "What is the genre of Matthew's Days?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2990332245826721,
            "question": "Are there any awards associated with Matthew's Days?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Witold Leszczy\u0144ski directed the film Matthew's Days.",
            "html": "yago_17416_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the genre of Matthew's Days?",
            "html": "yago_17416_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of work did Witold Leszczy\u0144ski create?",
            "html": "yago_17416_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was Matthew's Days filmed?",
            "html": "yago_17416_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17416_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17416_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17416_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17416_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17416_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17416_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17416_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17416_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17416_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17416_87.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that confirms Witold Leszczy\u0144ski as the director of the film \"Matthew's Days\", with various sources mentioning him as the director, such as Wikipedia, IMDb, and OVGuide."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly state that \"Matthew's Days\" (Polish: \u017bywot Mateusza) is a 1968 Polish drama film directed by Witold Leszczy\u0144ski. Therefore, the statement \"Witold Leszczy\u0144ski directed the film Matthew's Days\" is supported by the provided information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}